interconnectit.com 2018-09-11

# Privacy Statement | interconnect/it

We’ve always taken your privacy seriously and we will continue to do so. Our simple but thorough approach means that you don’t need to worry about us doing anything that might be considered detrimental to your privacy. 

These include the following guidelines:

## GDPR

We are registered with the ICO and comply with General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) in all our dealings with your personal data.

## Use and collection of personal information

In general you can visit our website without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself.  If, however, you use our site to submit a job application or use our contact form, download the Search Replace script, or purchase one of our products, you will be asked to provide certain information such as but not limited to, your contact details. We will store this data and hold it on computer or otherwise.

We may use information that you provide:

  * To answer any queries you submit.
  * For assessment and analysis, e.g. marketing, customer and product analysis, to enable us to review, develop and improve our services.
  * For our recruitment campaigns.

We will never sell or give your data to third parties without your prior permission, however, we may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a legal duty to disclose or share your personal data, in order to comply with or meet any legal obligation.

## Cookies

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways.  One way is through our use of ‘cookies’. Most websites use cookies in order to make them work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the website.  They help us to understand how our customers and potential customers use our website so we can develop and improve the design, layout, content and function of the site. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by websites that you visit.  They save and retrieve pieces of information about your visit to the website – for example, how you entered the site, how you navigated through the site and what information and documentation was of interest to you. Some of our cookies are used to simply collect information about how visitors use our website and these types of cookies collect the information in an anonymous form.

By using our site, you agree to our use of Cookies.

## Hotjar

We use[ Hotjar](http://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimise this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behaviour and their devices (in particular a device’s IP address captured and stored only in anonymised form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymised user profile. Neither Hotjar nor ourselves will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking [here](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy). 

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this[ opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

## Requests

You have the right to see personal data (as defined by GDPR) that we keep about you upon receipt of a written request.  Any request should be emailed FAO David Coveney to support@interconnectit.com.
